- Lf and when?
- Maybe we should change the subject.
(Penny:)Amy, how are your lady parts?
Still chilly down there?
(Bernadette:)Hang on. None of Sheldon's theories
have ever been definitively proven.
(Bernadette:)My husband actually went
to outer space.
(Amy:)That's an impressive accomplishment.
(Amy:)He's now an inspiration
to millions of Americans...
(Amy:)...who know you don't have to be special
or even qualified to go into space.
(Penny:)You know, I remember the first time
I got a bikini wax.
(Penny:)My sister did it with melted Crayolas
and duct tape.
Yeah, it's a bad idea.
(Bernadette:)Gosh, Amy. I'm sensing a little hostility.
(Bernadette:)Is it maybe because, like Sheldon's work,
your sex life is also theoretical?
(Penny:)Damn.
(Amy:)Well, at least when we do make love...
(Amy:)...Sheldon won't be thinking
about his mother.